const personalityJson = {
	"[없음]":{
		"back":"",
		"front":""
	},
	"검은달의": {
		"each": "aura_s_fullmoon",
		"back": "back_a",
		"front": "front_a"
	},
	"겁이 많은":{
        	"back":"aura_a_mint",
        	"front":"a"
    	},
	"고귀한":{
	        "back":"aura_s_star",
	        "front":"aura_s_star2"
	},
	"고독한":{
	        "back":"aura_a2_warmgray",
	        "front":"a2"
	},
	"고집있는":{
	        "back":"aura_b_navy",
	        "front":""
	},
	"광적인":{
	        "back":"aura_s_purplelight",
	        "front":"aura_s_purplelight"
	},
	"귀여운": {
		"each": "aura_s_stardust",
		"back": "back_b",
		"front": "front_b"
	},
	"그림자달의": {
		"each": "aura_s_fullmoon",
		"back": "back_c",
		"front": "front_c"
	},
	"기품있는":{
	        "back":"aura_s_blackhole",
	        "front":"aura_s_star"
	},
	"깨끗한":{
	        "back":"aura_s_transparent3",
	        "front":"aura_s_star"
	},
	"끈기있는": {
		"each": "aura_s_persistent_lively",
		"back": "back_a",
		"front": "front_a"
	},
	"나만의":{
	},
	"내향적인":{
	        "back":"aura_a2_red",
	        "front":"a2"
	},
	"냉정한":{
	        "back":"aura_b_blue",
	        "front":""
	},
	"노력하는":{
	        "back":"aura_b_darkbrown",
	        "front":""
	},
	"눈치빠른":{
	        "back":"aura_b_yellowgreen",
	        "front":""
	},
	"대담한":{
	        "back":"aura_b_sky",
	        "front":""
	},
	"덜렁대는":{
	        "back":"aura_b_orange",
	        "front":""
	},
	"따뜻한":{
	        "back":"aura_s_xmas_b",
	        "front":"aura_s_xmas_b"
	},
	"똑똑한":{
	        "back":"aura_b_mint",
	        "front":""
	},
	"명랑한":{
	        "back":"aura_a2_orange",
	        "front":"a2"
	},
	"명예로운":{
	        "back":"aura_s_pvp_a",
	        "front":"aura_s_pvp_a"
	},
	"몰입하는":{
	        "back":"aura_s_universe2",
	        "front":"aura_s_universe2"
	},
	"몽환적인": {
		"each": "aura_s_dreamlike_enigmatic",
		"back": "back_a",
		"front": "front_a"
	},
	"무모한": {
		"each": "aura_a4",
		"back": "back_b",
		"front": "front_a"
	},
	"미지의":{
	        "back":"aura_s_universe3",
	        "front":"aura_s_universe3"
	},
	"변덕쟁이":{
	        "back":"aura_b_purple",
	        "front":""
	},
	"보름달의":{
	        "back":"aura_s_moon_yellow",
	        "front":"aura_s_transparent_yellow"
	},
	"보름달의 (비행)":{
	        "back":"aura_s_moon_yellow_fly",
	        "front":"aura_s_transparent_yellow_fly"
	},
	"부족한":{
	        "back":"aura_a_navypurple",
	        "front":"a3_purple"
	},
	"붉은달의": {
		"each": "aura_s_fullmoon",
		"back": "back_b",
		"front": "front_b"
	},
	"비밀스러운": {
		"each": "aura_s_arcane",
		"back": "back",
		"front": "front"
	},
	"사교적인":{
	        "back":"aura_a_pastelpink",
	        "front":"a3_purple"
	},
	"사나운":{
	        "back":"aura_s_blackred",
	        "front":"aura_s_blackred"
	},
	"사랑스러운":{
	        "back":"aura_a_babypink",
	        "front":"a"
	},
	"산만한":{
	        "back":"aura_s_mint",
	        "front":"aura_s_champion2"
	},
	"서투른":{
	        "back":"aura_a2_purple",
	        "front":"a2"
	},
	"섬뜩한":{
	        "back":"aura_s_halloween_b",
	        "front":"aura_s_halloween_b"
	},
	"섬뜩한 (비행)":{
	        "back":"aura_s_halloween_b_fly",
	        "front":"aura_s_halloween_b"
	},
	"성급한":{
	        "back":"aura_b_orangered",
	        "front":""
	},
	"성실한":{
	        "back":"aura_a_lapislazuli",
	        "front":"a"
	},
	"성탄의":{
	        "back":"aura_s_xmas_a",
	        "front":"aura_s_xmas_a"
	},
	"소극적인":{
	        "back":"aura_a_orange",
	        "front":"a"
	},
	"소원의": {
		"each": "aura_s_wishful",
		"back": "back",
		"front": "front"
	},
	"수수께끼의": {
		"each": "aura_s_dreamlike_enigmatic",
		"back": "back_b",
		"front": "front_b"
	},
	"수줍은":{
	        "back":"aura_b_whight",
	        "front":""
	},
	"순수한":{
	        "back":"aura_s_transparent",
	        "front":"aura_s_transparent"
	},
	"순진한" : {
	        "each" : "aura_s_innocent",
	        "back" : "back",
	        "front" : "front"
	},
	"신나는": {
		"each": "aura_s_exciting_blithe",
		"back": "back_a",
		"front": "front_a"
	},
	"신비의":{
	        "back":"aura_a2_greenmint",
	        "front":"a2_l"
	},
	"신중한":{
	        "back":"aura_b_black",
	        "front":""
	},
	"실력좋은":{
	        "back":"aura_s_game_a",
	        "front":"aura_s_game_a"
	},
	"심약한":{
	        "back":"aura_s_blackgreen",
	        "front":"aura_s_blackgreen"
	},
	"심연의":{
	        "back":"aura_s_abyss",
	        "front":"aura_s_abyss"
	},
	"심판의": {
	        "each": "aura_s_judgement",
	        "back": "back",
	        "front": "front"
	},
	"애교많은":{
	        "back":"aura_a_yellow",
	        "front":"a"
	},
	"어두운":{
	        "back":"aura_a2_brown",
	        "front":"a2_copper"
	},
	"여명의":{
	        "back":"aura_a2_white",
	        "front":"a2_whitegold"
	},
	"열망의": {
		"each": "aura_s_hopeful",
		"back": "back_a",
		"front": "front_a"
	},
	"영광의":{
	        "back":"aura_s_pvp_b",
	        "front":"aura_s_pvp_b"
	},
	"영리한" : {
	        "each" : "aura_s_smart",
	        "back" : "back",
	        "front" : "front"
	},
	"오만한":{
	        "back":"aura_a_red",
	        "front":"a"
	},
	"오싹한":{
	        "back":"aura_s_halloween_a",
	        "front":"aura_s_halloween_a"
	},
	"오싹한 (비행)":{
	        "back":"aura_s_halloween_a_fly",
	        "front":"aura_s_halloween_a"
	},
	"온순한":{
	        "back":"aura_b_green",
	        "front":""
	},
	"완벽주의자":{
	        "back":"aura_s_universe1",
	        "front":"aura_s_universe1"
	},
	"외로워하는":{
	        "back":"aura_a_lavender",
	        "front":"a"
	},
	"외향적인":{
	        "back":"aura_s_prism",
	        "front":"aura_s_prism"
	},
	"용감한":{
	        "back":"aura_b_red",
	        "front":""
	},
	"유능한":{
	        "back":"aura_s_bluelight",
	        "front":"aura_s_bluelight"
	},
	"은총의": {
		"each": "aura_s_blessing",
		"back": "back",
		"front": "front"
	},
	"자애로운" : {
	        "back" : "aura_a2_pink",
	        "front" : "a2"
	},
	"장난스러운" : {
	        "each" : "aura_s_stardust",
	        "back" : "back_a",
	        "front" : "front_a"
	},
	"재능있는":{
	        "back":"aura_s_game_b",
	        "front":"aura_s_game_b"
	},
	"재앙의":{
	        "back":"aura_s_dark",
	        "front":"aura_s_dark"
	},
	"정화의": {
	        "each": "aura_s_purifying",
	        "back": "back",
	        "front": "front"
	},
	"정확한":{
	        "back":"aura_a_blacknavy",
	        "front":"a3_blue"
	},
	"조용한":{
	        "back":"aura_a2_darkblue",
	        "front":"a2"
	},
	"종말의":{
	        "back":"aura_s_end",
	        "front":"aura_s_end"
	},
	"즐거운": {
		"each": "aura_s_exciting_blithe",
		"back": "back_b",
		"front": "front_b"
	},
	"차분한":{
	        "back":"aura_b_brown",
	        "front":""
	},
	"천진난만한":{
	        "back":"aura_b_yellow",
	        "front":""
	},
	"청량한": {
		"each": "aura_s_refreshing",
		"back": "back",
		"front": "front"
	},
	"촐랑대는":{
	        "back":"aura_b_pink",
	        "front":""
	},
	"탐식의":{
	        "back":"aura_s_greedy",
	        "front":"aura_s_greedy"
	},
	"평범한":{
	        "back":"aura_a_babyblue",
	        "front":"a"
	},
	"푸른달의":{
	        "back":"aura_s_moon_blue",
	        "front":"aura_s_transparent_blue"
	},
	"푸른달의 (비행)":{
	        "back":"aura_s_moon_blue_fly",
	        "front":"aura_s_transparent_blue_fly"
	},
	"품위있는":{
	        "back":"aura_s_pearl",
	        "front":"aura_s_pearl"
	},
	"풍요로운":{
	        "back":"aura_e_emart",
	        "front":"aura_e_emart"
	},
	"피곤한" : {
	        "back" : "aura_a_skywhite",
	        "front" : "a3_skywhite"
	},
	"호기심많은":{
	        "back":"aura_a2_green",
	        "front":"a2"
	},
	"혼돈의":{
	        "back":"aura_s_blackblue",
	        "front":"aura_s_blackblue"
	},
	"화가 많은": {
		"each": "aura_a4",
		"back": "back_a",
		"front": "front_a"
	},
	"환상의": {
		"each": "aura_s_hopeful",
		"back": "back_c",
		"front": "front_c"
	},
	"활기찬": {
		"each": "aura_s_persistent_lively",
		"back": "back_b",
		"front": "front_b"
	},
	"황야의":{
	        "back":"aura_s_sunset",
	        "front":"aura_s_sunset"
	},
	"희망의": {
		"each": "aura_s_hopeful",
		"back": "back_b",
		"front": "front_b"
	}
}
